mydamnchannel.com 2016-03-14

# My Damn Channel » Privacy Policy

My Damn Channel operates www.MyDamnChannel.com and related services, applications, domains and networks offered by My Damn Channel ("My Damn Channel Service"). The My Damn Channel Service allows you to view, comment on, and share audiovisual content with other users of the My Damn Channel Service community on the Internet. My Damn Channel’s Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using the My Damn Channel Service.

By using or accessing the My Damn Channel Service, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

## **Children Under 13:**

IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE My Damn Channel SERVICE AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER.

My Damn Channel complies with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act and does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to or on the My Damn Channel Service. If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 who has become a member of the My Damn Channel Service, then please contact My Damn Channel at [info@MyDamnChannel.com](mailto:info@MyDamnChannel.com) to have that child’s account terminated and information deleted.

## **What information does My Damn Channel collect?**

For visitors to our website and registered users, we log standard technical information, such as your IP address. If you choose to register with us, My Damn Channel requires you to provide your name, email address, and each user has a user ID and password that they choose. To maintain privacy it is important not to share your password with anyone. Selecting a longer password with a mix of letters, numbers and symbols makes it more difficult for others to guess your password. It is also helpful to change passwords on a regular basis. In addition, for registered users, My Damn Channel will require you to provide geographical information such as your physical address. In the future My Damn Channel may ask you to provide other demographic information, such as age, gender, interests or occupation. We may collect other personal information when you provide feedback or comments, or communicate with others through our systems. My Damn Channel also uses "cookies" – small files containing a string of characters sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser – in addition to web beacons – one-pixel, GIF images used for gathering and sharing information used to administer the My Damn Channel Service website and provide a more tailored and user-friendly service to you. For example, we may use cookies or web beacons to count the number of unique computers accessing our website. You can set your browser to refuse cookies from the My Damn Channel Service if you choose. When you access the My Damn Channel Service or open one of our HTML emails, or newsletters for registered users, we may automatically record certain information from your system by using different types of tracking technology. This "automatically collected" information may include IP Address, a unique device or user ID, version of software installed, system type, the content and pages that you access on the My Damn Channel Service, and the dates and times that you visit the My Damn Channel Service. 

## **How does My Damn Channel use your information?**

The information we collect about you in the course of our relationship is used to provide the My Damn Channel Service to you. For example, as we endeavor to protect your identity, we may use your demographic information to create a database of user profiles, select advertisements based on your information and for marketing analysis. In addition, we look at technical information to diagnose problems with our systems, to administer the My Damn Channel Service, and to enhance the services we provide to you. We may use your information to track user-submitted content and users to the extent necessary to comply as a service provider with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act. If you have registered with the My Damn Channel Service, we may use your email address, without further consent, for administrative communications such as notifying you of major updates, for customer service purposes, to address copyright infringement or defamation issues, or to contact you regarding any content on the My Damn Channel Service. 

My Damn Channel uses all of the information that we collect to understand the usage trends and preferences of our users, to improve the way the My Damn Channel Service works and looks, and to create new features and functionality. My Damn Channel may use "automatically collected" information, "cookies", and web beacons to: (a) automatically update the My Damn Channel Service service; (b) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you access the My Damn Channel Service; (c) monitor aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages accessed; and (d) track your entries, submissions, participation and status in any promotions or other activities, and usage of the My Damn Channel Service. 

## **When does My Damn Channel disclose information?**

My Damn Channel does not share your personally identifiable information, including any of your user profile data that you create, with other organizations for their marketing or promotional uses. Please be aware, however, that any personally identifiable information that you voluntarily choose to display on the My Damn Channel Service becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others without restriction. 

My Damn Channel may share personally identifiable information about our users with third parties, including: (a) with your consent or as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy; (b) when we have a good faith belief it is necessary pursuant to a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order; (c) where required by law; or (d) at our sole discretion, where we deem necessary to respond to claims, to protect the safety of any individual or the public, or to protect the rights or property of the My Damn Channel Service or any third party.

We may disclose personally identifiable information to affiliated companies, sub-contractors, other agents or businesses or persons to: provide web site hosting, maintenance, and security services; fulfill orders; conduct data analysis and create reports; offer certain functionality; and assist My Damn Channel in improving the My Damn Channel Service and creating new service features. We require that these parties process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy, we authorize only a limited use of such information, and we require these parties to use reasonable confidentiality measures to keep your information secure. My Damn Channel may also disclose to third parties anonymous aggregated user information that is not personally identifiable. 

## **How to change or delete your information?**

You have the ability and control to remove or alter your account-specific information, including any user profile data that you provide to the My Damn Channel Service at any time. Access and control over most user-provided personal information on the My Damn Channel Service is readily available through the edit function on your profile. As a user of the My Damn Channel Service, you may modify or remove any of your profile information at any time by logging into your account. Information will be updated promptly. If you wish to deactivate your My Damn Channel Service account, you may do so by emailing [info@MyDamnChannel.com](mailto:info@MyDamnChannel.com). Removed information such as your user ID, geographical information connected to your user ID, and any content that you have uploaded to the My Damn Channel Service may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time, but will not be generally accessible by My Damn Channel or users of the My Damn Channel service. 

## **How does My Damn Channel keep your information secure?**

My Damn Channel will take appropriate security measures designed to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. My Damn Channel processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. My Damn Channel takes reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

We endeavor to restrict access to personal information to My Damn Channel employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and are required to meet these obligations. 

If My Damn Channel learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. My Damn Channel may post a notice on the My Damn Channel Service if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach you should notify us at [info@MyDamnChannel.com](mailto:info@MyDamnChannel.com). 

## **What do I need to know about third party sites, co-branded sites, and My Damn Channel’s business partners?**

My Damn Channel may establish relationships that allow visitors to the My Damn Channel Service to go directly to sites operated by third parties. Some of these sites may be co-branded with our logos; however, they are not operated or maintained by My Damn Channel. We are not responsible for the content or practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to the My Damn Channel Service. These links are meant for the user’s convenience only. Links to third party sites do not constitute our sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the content, policies or practices of such third party sites. Once you have left the My Damn Channel Service via such a link, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party site.

We may use third parties to manage contests, chats or other features, and these parties may have access to contact information submitted by visitors who participate in those activities.

## **Does My Damn Channel use third party ad servers?**

My Damn Channel uses third party advertising companies and advertising networks to deliver advertisements on the My Damn Channel Service. These companies may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements’ effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these companies is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this Privacy Policy.

## **In the Event of Merger or Sale**

In the event that My Damn Channel is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, or undergoes a change of control or any form of sale or transfer of some or all of its assets, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from users as part of that merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

## **Changes and Updates to this Privacy Notice**

Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when we received that personal information. Your continued use of the My Damn Channel Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions.

For revisions to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information you have provided to us, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you and obtain your consent before implementing revisions with respect to such information. 

## **Contacting My Damn Channel**

Please contact My Damn Channel with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your personal information, and our third-party disclosure practices or your consent choices at: 630 Ninth Ave, Suite 212, New York, NY 10036 or by email: [info@MyDamnChannel.com](mailto:info@MyDamnChannel.com). We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days of its receipt. 

## Contacting My Damn Channel

Please contact My Damn Channel with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your personal information, and our third-party disclosure practices or your consent choices at: 202 W. 40th St., 16th Floor, New York, NY 10018 or by email: [info@MyDamnChannel.com](mailto:info@MyDamnChannel.com). We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days of its receipt.
